

CARLOS HUGUET

SENIOR IT ENGINEER

INTEREST AND HOBBIES

I'm a nice person who loves travel, play soccer with friends on tuesdays and play video games. In addition, I like to cook and I have taken some lessons about cooking.

However my passion is the photography, when I travel, I always take my camera and try to get nice pics.

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- People management
- Providers relationship
- Fluent english (B2)
- Main development skills: NodeJS, jest, dependencies injection, pattern design, git, gitlab, jenkins, docker, javascript.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Cell: +34 66 00 33 434 email: huguet10@gmail.com Website: https://chuguet.github.io GitHub: https://github.com/chuguet LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/chuguet

ABOUT ME

Software Engineer with a Masters in Web Engineering from the Polytechnic University of Madrid and a passion for Computer Science. I have worked in the analysis, design and architecture of web applications for important companies in sports betting and banking sectors.

In the last years I have oriented and developed my professional career towards the banking sector along with the development of software and web engineering, realizing successful projects across leading websites and pioneers in the current market.

I have been also working as technical leader managing teams and people. As manager, I've had to gather metrics, motivate the team and drive the team to a common target. KAIZEN (Today better than yesterday, tomorrow better than today)

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Denizen Financial at BBVA SA

EU Team Lead (mar. 2019 - currently)

Software IT Architect (may. 2018 - mar. 2019)

Senior IT Engineer (aug. 2016 - may. 2018)

ING Bank

Full stack developer (jun. 2014 - jul. 2016)

Factoria ETSIA SL

Senior programmer (jan. 2012 - may. 2014)

Coritel

Junior programmer (aug. 2011 - dec. 2011)

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Masters in Web Engineering

Polytechnic University of Madrid (2014 - 2015)

Software Engineer Degree

Pontifical University of Salamanca (2012 - 2014)

Technical Software Engineer Degree

University of Málaga (2007 - 2011)